### PERSONAL PROFILE

As a mobile app (Android & iOS) and web developer, I have two years of experience, supplemented by internships and personal projects. My goal is to continue advancing in the field of development by working on innovative projects and staying at the forefront of emerging technologies.

# CONTACT INFORMATION

karimdiawara96@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/karim-diawara-8466b2208/



https://github.com/kdiawara96



https://karimdiawara.netlify.app/

## SKILLS

# **Coding Languages:**

Dart, Java, PHP(basic), HTML/CSS ,Type Script

## Model:

MVC, MVVM

### Framework / CMS:

Flutter, Angular, Ionic, Spring Boot, CMS(WordPress), Bootstrap

## Others:

FireBase, Figma, Git/GiHub, GitLab, Docker

### Languages:

• Bambara: Very good

• French: Very good

• English: Passable

# REFERENCES

Name: Fatoumata Kaloga

Company: Orange Digital Center

e-mail: fatidiof@gmail.com

Name Issif Diawara

Company: McDonald's France

e-mail: issifdiawara@gmail.com

### HOBBIES

Manga | Sports | Literature

# **KARIM DIAWARA**

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **EWAATI**

**FULL-STACK WEB & MOBILE DEVELOPER** 

#### **FIXED-TERM CONTRACT**

APRIL 2023 - ONGOING

- e-learning (en cours)
- Machine management
- Showcase site (ml-trustservices.com)

### **WASSA TECHNOLOGIE**

WEBSITE AND MOBILE APPLICATION DEVELOPER

#### INTERN

**DECEMBER 2021 - MARCH 2022** 

- The Sahelian Hydraulic Bureau (BSH) website and the Malian Psychology Organization (OMP) are two showcase sites representing their company.
- MyStore allows you to store products and display them in order of urgency and by date...
- Weather allows you to have all the weather data thanks to an API (Weather API) and in real time.

### KELECE

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

### **VOLUNTEERING**

MARCH 2021 TO JULY 2021

- Participation in the development of SPORTECH software
- Data collection

# TRAINING

# Institut Universitaire de Gestion de Bamako (IUG)

2017 - 2020

Professional degree in Management IT

### Kénédougou High School of Sikasso

2016 - 2017

Malian Baccalaureate in Economic Science.

# IMPROVEMENT

### **ORANGE DIGITAL CENTER:**

Full-Stack Developer

June 1, 2022 - March 7, 2023

- Draw API
- Region Management API
- Error Rating API
- An application for Orange Digital Center (ERP)
- A Showcase Website
- Mobile application (iOS, Android) called Kodomo

### PROFIL PERSONNEL

En tant que développeur d'applications mobiles (Android & iOS) et de sites web, j'ai deux ans d'expérience, complétée par des stages et des projets personnels. Mon objectif est de continuer à progresser dans le domaine du développement, en travaillant sur des projets innovants et en restant à la pointe des technologies émergentes.

# COORDONNÉES

karimdiawara96@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/karim-diawara-8466b2208/



https://github.com/kdiawara96



https://karimdiawara.netlify.app/

# COMPÉTENCES

# Langages de codage:

Dart, Java, PHP(basique), HTML/CSS, Type Script

## Model:

MVC, MVVM

### Framework / CMS:

Flutter, Angular, Ionic, Spring Boot, CMS(WordPress), Bootstrap

### **Autres**

FireBase, Figma, Git/GiHub, GitLab, Docker

### Langues:

Bambara : Très-bienFrançais : Très-Bien

• Anglais : Assez-bien

# RÉFÉRENCES

Nom: Fatoumata Kaloga

Travail: Orange Digital Center

e-mail: fatidiof@gmail.com

**Nom:** Issif Diawara

Travail: McDonald's France

e-mail: issifdiawara@gmail.com

### LOISIRS

Manga | Sports | Lecture

# **KARIM DIAWARA**

# DÉVELOPPEUR DE LOGICIEL

## EXPÉRIENCES DE TRAVAIL

#### **EWAATI**

**DÉVELOPPEUR FULL-STACK WEB & MOBILE** 

#### CDD

AVRIL 2023 - EN COURS

- e-learning (en cours)
- Gestion d'engins
- Site vitrine (ml-trustservices.com)

### **WASSA TECHNOLOGIE**

DÉVELOPPEUR DE SITE WEB ET D'APPLICATION MOBILE

### **STAGIAIRE**

DÉCEMBRE 2021 - MARS 2022

- Le Site web <u>Bureau sahelien d'hydraulique</u> (BSH) et l'<u>Organisation Malienne de Psychologie</u> (OMP) sont deux sites vitrine représentant leur entreprise.
- MyStore permet de stocker les produits et les affichés en ordre de cas d'urgent et par date...
- Weather permet d'avoir toutes les données météo grâce à une API (Weather API) et en temps réel.

### KELECE

DÉVELOPPEUR DE LOGICIEL

### **BÉNÉVOLAT**

MARS 2021 À JUILLET 2021

- Participation au développement du logiciel SPORTECH
- Collection des données

# FORMATIONS

# Institut Universitaire de Gestion de Bamako (IUG)

2017 - 2020

Licence professionnelle en Informatique de gestion

### Lycée Kénédougou de Sikasso

2016 - 2017

Baccalauréat Malien en Science Economique.

### PERFECTIONNEMENT

### **ORANGE DIGITAL CENTER:**

Développeur Full-Stack 1 Juin 2022 - 07 Mars 2023

- Api Tirage
- Api Gestion des régions
- Api Erreur note
- Une application pour Orange Digital Center (ERP)
- Un site Vitrine
- Application mobile (iOS, Android) appelé Kodomo